https://www.quiltwoman.com/privacy-policy

Wholesale
My Cart1: 0 Items ($0.00)
BL2 - Beaquilter - Bea Lee
BPQD - Back Porch Quilts and Designs, LLC - Vicki Hesseltine
DBM - Design And Be Mary - Mary Mittelstadt
DCM - Debbie's Creative Moments - Debbie Caffrey & Charlotte Angotti
GR - Gail's Quilts - Gail Ruminski
GTD - Golden Thyme Designs & L and L Studios - Lacey J. Hill
BL2 - Beaquilter - Bea Lee
BPQD - Back Porch Quilts and Designs, LLC - Vicki Hesseltine
DBM - Design And Be Mary - Mary Mittelstadt
DCM - Debbie's Creative Moments - Debbie Caffrey & Charlotte Angotti
GR - Gail's Quilts - Gail Ruminski
GTD - Golden Thyme Designs & L and L Studios - Lacey J. Hill
BL2 - Beaquilter - Bea Lee
BPQD - Back Porch Quilts and Designs, LLC - Vicki Hesseltine
DBM - Design And Be Mary - Mary Mittelstadt
DCM - Debbie's Creative Moments - Debbie Caffrey & Charlotte Angotti
GR - Gail's Quilts - Gail Ruminski
GTD - Golden Thyme Designs & L and L Studios - Lacey J. Hill
Mailing List
Two easy ways to join our mailing list! Text QUILTWOMAN to 22828 to get started. or
For Email Marketing you can trust
QuiltWoman.com
120 West Albion St.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the QuiltWoman.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our weekly email as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Home
Testimonials
Site Map
About Us
Contact Us
Downloadable Patterns
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
